<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BryanPH</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>https://bryanph.com</link>
    <atom:link href="https://bryanph.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 00:13:06 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 00:13:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.2.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Yahoo Released Everything Before They Even Got Breached</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 18:22:01 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/06/yahoothreeletters.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/06/yahoothreeletters.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>2016 Verizon Breach Report</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 12:46:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/05/verizonbreach.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/05/verizonbreach.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Massive 1Tbps DDOS Attack</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 07:46:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/05/ovhddos.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/security/2016/10/05/ovhddos.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>security</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hubble's View of the Bubble Nebula</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 07:46:23 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/space/2016/10/05/bubblenebula.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/space/2016/10/05/bubblenebula.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>space</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Intellectual Isolation</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Lately I have been feeling rather down, and I have had to do some soul searching to figure out the cause. Everything has been going amazing to the casual observer, and the truth is that I can’t really disagree. But even yet, I’m still waking up sad in the morning and struggling with internal feelings. I am motivated and I see the beauty in life; I haven’t given up hope and I know the future is wide. Rather, I have gotten more and more lonely as time as gone on waiting for something in that future that I can’t quite pick out. This latest round of huge life changes that have occurred recently have opened my eyes to something that is difficult for me to deal with. I suffer from a loneliness derived from lack of intellectual connection.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My new job is amazing, by all accounts. It’s something which I have wanted to do for a long time and am finally able to see potential for myself in. But it comes with a huge caveat. I can’t talk about what I do with anyone outside of my office. As someone who lives for their work, who cares almost exclusively about technology and progression, I come off as rather dry and boring of a conversationalist to anyone not interested in tech or it’s culture. I also happen to live in the middle of the midwest; where people still think that knowing how a computer works is some sort of black magic. That makes finding people to connect with on that basis more of a challenge than anything else. That issue is only compounded by the fact that people in similar industry are naturally reclusive and difficult to interact with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to only talk about my work with people, but that is where the vast majority of my time and energy is dedicated. It only follows that most of my interests outside of work are somehow along the same vein. I look for people to interact with, who I can find common ground and connection, but they are illusive and rare as can be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am lucky to not actually be alone, to have close friends who are supportive and committed. It helps immensely to have people near by who you can trust and hold close. I appreciate them deeply, and I think they understand how I feel towards them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As wonderful as those things are, it still doesn’t help when you feel like you have no one to really click with and converse. When I was younger I felt a very similar isolation as a result of social awkwardness and peer relations, and my solution then was to dive deeply into the internet and find solace with people who didn’t know anything about me and couldn’t tell I was a child. I hung out and made great friends on IRC and in games like CyberNations. I remember getting my first headset so I could play Halo 2 and Skype with people at the same time. The people who I interacted with then were far away, to the point that it didn’t matter where any of us were or came from. The connection was deep because we shared so much experience together and spent so much time entertaining our similar interests. Those were fantastic times that saved me from a lot of anguish and further failures in my social development. Now that I am older though, I find it much more difficult to create those connections and maintain them. I can no longer find solace alone in my room on a computer, with only the vague gestures pixels to remind me there is a human on the other side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Going to DefCon was an amazing experience for me, because it felt like I had found my herd. I could walk up to anyone and not just learn from them, but also have meaningful conversation that felt like the ramifications could be real and useful in the world. Virtually everyone was some level of weird or awkward, but I knew that I could walk into a group and most of the individuals had grown with the same culture that influenced me during my developmental years. The shared culture was amazing, and it did give me a sense of belonging which I deeply lacked previously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I face the same issues of intellectual isolation that have haunted me this whole time. But instead of growing to be satisfied, I have become greedy in my wishes for those feelings to well up inside me from interactions IRL. I am now, and perhaps forever, always searching for those who I can talk to and find commonality with. I also want for a deeper physical relationship in life, but unlike the experiences I have had thus far, I want it to be based on something more than gross, obvious attraction. I think knowing what I want is probably one of the healthiest ways I can imagine approaching these issues, but it doesn’t stop the short term pain and grievance. I have to continually remind myself of why I feel the way I do and what it is I’m searching for instead of constantly numbing the pain in a lame attempt to forget my core directive. It helps a ton to put things down in writing, because at least then I can muster up the courage to face my sadness head on.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 06:18:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/personal/2016/10/05/intellectualisolation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/personal/2016/10/05/intellectualisolation.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>personal</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Notes on the VP Debate</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;What’s up with the nominees switching colors all the time? Is this normal since the first presidential debate?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 06:18:20 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://bryanph.com/politics/2016/10/05/vpdebate.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://bryanph.com/politics/2016/10/05/vpdebate.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>politics</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
